<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE help SYSTEM "../../../include/dtd/help.dtd">
<help title="XAMS Accounts" xams-release="0.0.9" file-release="0.0.9" file-revision="1" date="2002-11-29">
    <lngspec name="english" iso="en" localname="english"/>
    <skindir>{{skindir}}</skindir>
    <maintainers>
        <maintainer>
            <name>XAMS Core-Team</name>
            <email>info@xams.org</email>
        </maintainer>
    </maintainers>    
    <information>
        XAMS reaches a maximum of flexibility and functionality in the
        sector of administration because of its special grouping system. There are
        three different kinds of management instances called "Administrators",
        "Resellers" and "Customers".
    </information>
    <section>
        <head>Administrators</head>
        <description>
            An Administrator can take up changes on all data without
            any limitations. He has total access to every function of XAMS and thus
            can administrate all Resellers and where required even whose Customers.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Resellers</head>
        <description>
            An Administrator assigns any desired sites definitely to
            one Reseller. These sites then can be just administrated by this special Reseller.
            Here, he has to keep to the limitations given by the Administrator. He may
            apply - according to the limits - any desired Customers and also manage
            them. 
            In contrast to the Administrator, he cannot take up changes to the
            system settings, to the field-configuration in the addressbook and
            it is not possible for him to analyse the database.
            In addition to that he cannot gain access to the customers belonging
            to another Reseller of course.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Customers</head>
        <description>
            A Reseller (resp. Administrator) assigns any desired sites 
            to a Customer. These sites then can be administrated by the Customer.
            Here, he has to keep to the limitations given by the Reseller (resp.
            Administrator). He may apply - according to the limits - any desired
            users or aliases and also manage them.
            In contrast to the Reseller, he cannot gain access to the users or
            aliases belonging to another Customer of course.
        </description>
    </section>
</help>