<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE help SYSTEM "../../../include/dtd/help.dtd">
<help title="Alias-Addressbook Administration" xams-release="0.0.9" file-release="0.0.9" file-revision="1" date="2002-11-29">
    <lngspec name="english" iso="en" localname="english"/>
    <skindir>{{skindir}}</skindir>
    <maintainers>
        <maintainer>
            <name>XAMS Core-Team</name>
            <email>info@xams.org</email>
        </maintainer>
    </maintainers>    
    <information>
        The XAMS Addressbook is designed to create an Addressbook for Sites,
    	Users, Aliases, Resellers and Customers. The Fields for the
    	addressbook (e.g. Name, Street, ...) must be created by you, allowing
    	you to define exactly the fields you want or need for each system.
    </information>
    <section>
        <head>Fieldname</head>
        <description>
        	Enter a fieldname that should be available to your Alias-Addressbook.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>LDAP</head>
        <description>
            With LDAP (Lightweight Directory Access Protocol) XAMS provides the
            ability to export specific addressbook-fields into such database.
            This LDAP database can be used by different applications as a global
            addressbook.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>ACL Reseller</head>
        <description>
            The ACL Reseller (Access Control List) is used for limiting access
            of resellers to this field. The option "None" disables all access
            rights for the Reseller (no read or write access). "Read" or "Read+Write"
            allow the Reseller to read or even modify this field.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>ACL Customer</head>
        <description>
            Same as ACL Reseller - you can set access rights for your Customers here.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Move Field</head>
        <description>
        	This function changes the order of how the fields should appear in
        	the interface. The selectbox shows every existing Fieldname; select
        	an entry to move the current field below the selected field.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Delete</head>
        <description>
        	If you activate the selectbox in any line and click update the selected
        	lines will be deleted. NOTE: Data of all Aliases, that were in those fields
        	will be deleted!
        </description>
    </section>
</help>
