<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE help SYSTEM "../../../include/dtd/help.dtd">
<help title="Alias Management" xams-release="0.0.15" file-release="0.0.9" file-revision="1" date="2004-01-29">
    <lngspec name="english" iso="en" localname="english"/>
    <skindir>{{skindir}}</skindir>
    <maintainers>
        <maintainer>
            <name>XAMS Core-Team</name>
            <email>info@xams.org</email>
        </maintainer>
    </maintainers>    
    <information>
        The alias is an extra e-mail address. It is not a real e-mail account;
        all mail sent to the alias address is passed on to a designated real
        email account (or to another alias).
    </information>
    <section>
        <head>Site Name</head>
        <description>
            Choose the site to which an alias should be added.
            The alias is valid for all domains contained in a given site.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Incoming Address</head>
        <description>
            Just like a real email account, the alias is composed of the portion
            that comes before the @ symbol in the email address. From outside XAMS
            it cannot be determined whether an address is an alias or a real account.
            By entering a single asterisk * in this field, the alias will function
            as a "catch-all" address. All messages sent to the site in question that
            do not match existing users or aliases will be directed to the catch-all
            address.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Forward Address</head>
        <description>
            Messages sent to the alias will be routed to the e-mail address
            specified here. If the destination address is located in the same site,
            only the part before the @ symbol has to be specified. Otherwise the
            entire e-mail address, including the domain, must be indicated.
            In this field several addresses can be specified, separated by commas.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Bounce and Forward</head>
        <description>
            If this field is activated, messages addressed to this alias will
            be bounced (send back to the sender with an error message), but then
            the messages will actually be delivered to the "Forward Address."
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Blackhole</head>
        <description>
            If this field is activated, any messages addressed to this alias will
            be deleted immediately and cannot be recovered. This option is useful
            if a username or alias gets too much spam and needs to be retired.
        </description>
    </section>
</help>
