<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE help SYSTEM "../../../include/dtd/help.dtd">
<help title="Search" xams-release="0.0.9" file-release="0.0.9" file-revision="1" date="2002-11-29">
    <lngspec name="english" iso="en" localname="english"/>
    <skindir>{{skindir}}</skindir>
    <maintainers>
        <maintainer>
            <name>XAMS Core-Team</name>
            <email>info@xams.org</email>
        </maintainer>
    </maintainers>    
    <information>
        The XAMS-search helps you finding Sites, Domains, Users und Aliases
        by different search criterias.
    </information>
    <section>
        <head>Sitename</head>
        <description>
            Name of the Site container. It must be a systemwide unique name, which
            is set by an administrator or a reseller. A reseller can manage this container
            and can delegate it to an Customer. the contingents of the site can only be managed by 
            an administrator or a reseller.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Max. Quota in KB (each User)</head>
        <description>
            The maximum size of a mailbox of a single user in the site. Emails bigger than
            the size-limit will not be saved. The sender will get an according error message.
            A Customer can set a lower size limit to his users, but the maximum is this setting.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Max. Users</head>
        <description>
            This limits the number of Users a site is allowed to handle.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Max. Aliases</head>
        <description>
            The same as "Max. Users", but it limits the number of aliases.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Domainname</head>
        <description>
             Search-routine that filters by domainname (e.g. xams.org)
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Username</head>
        <description>
            Usually the email address of the user (the string he uses to login)
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>E-Mail Address</head>
        <description>
            Enter the full email address using the complete syntax
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Alias Name (Left Part)</head>
        <description>
            The string before the @-sign.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Alias Ziel (Right Part)</head>
        <description>
            Target address where the emails get redirected to if an alias was the
            actual address. if the target address is within the same site you can only
            set the local part (the string before the @ sign). else you should set the complete email address.
            You can also set multiple addresses delimited by a comma.
        </description>
    </section>
</help>
