<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE help SYSTEM "../../../include/dtd/help.dtd">
<help title="Site-Templates-Management" xams-release="0.0.16" file-release="0.0.9" file-revision="1" date="2004-06-14">
    <lngspec name="english" iso="en" localname="english"/>
    <skindir>{{skindir}}</skindir>
    <maintainers>
        <maintainer>
            <name>XAMS Core-Team</name>
            <email>info@xams.org</email>
        </maintainer>
    </maintainers>
    <information>
        A site is a kind of container which can imply one or more domains, users but
        also aliases.
        This container makes it possible that a user can have several e-mail addresses
        sharing all one "physical" (real) mailbox. For instance, there could be a site
        named "firm-name". In this container domains like "firm-name.com",
        "firm-name.net" but also "anothername.org" could be located.
        All users located in the container "firm-name" have in fact just one mailbox
        but can be reached via e-mail under "username@firm-name.com", "username@firm-name.net"
        and "user@anothername.org". For the user login (no matter if POP/IMAP, SMTP or direct in
        XAMS) it is just the same - every user name is valid. Of course this concept also applies
        to the aliases, except that no logons are possible with aliasname neither
        POP/IMAP/SMTP nor XAMS.
    </information>
    <section>
        <head>Template-Name</head>
        <description>
            This is the name of the template. This name shoulb be uniqe for each
            users.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Sitename</head>
        <description>
            This is the name of the container. It is solely visible for XAMS global admins as well
            as for the site admins. Administrator rights (for the site admins) can be given
            exclusively for this level, not - however - separately for domains, users or aliases.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Max. Quota</head>
        <description>
            This is the maximum mailbox size all users of this site can make use of.
            Is the maximum limit achieved by the sum of all Quotas, no more users
            can be added to this site.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Max. Quota (per User)</head>
        <description>
            This is the maximum mailbox size a single user can make use of. E-mails being
            bigger than the remaining space are not being saved. The sender thereby receives
            an according error notification. Furthermore, a customer can in fact give less quota
            to a user, but - however - not make more available than this limit gives.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Max. Users</head>
        <description>
            This is the maximum amount of users who can be created within this site.
            Only the global admin can change this value, a site admin has to be satisfied by the
            contingent made possible - he'll not be able to create more users when this limit
            is reached.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Max. Aliases</head>
        <description>
            Same as in point "Max. Users" - here, the maximum amount of aliases
            being available is specified. This value cannot be exceeded by a site admin.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Type</head>
        <description>
            Here is configured which kind of mailboxes the users may have within this site.
            If only POP3 is set here for instance, it is not possible making an IMAP-mailbox
            available for a user within this site.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Viruscheck</head>
        <description>
            Here you can determine for both incoming and outgoing mails within this
            site if they should be checked for viruses (by an external program).
            For the users within this site can be determined if the settings of
            the site should be taken over (inherited) or should be enabled or
            disabled in an explicit way.
            The settings of the site are bequeathed in standard.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Spamcheck</head>
        <description>
            Here you can determine for both incoming and outgoing mails within this
            site if they should be checked for spam (by an external program).
            For the users within this site can be determined if the settings of
            the site should be taken over (inherited) or should be enabled or
            disabled in an explicit way.
            The settings of the site are bequeathed in standard.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section>
        <head>Aliases 1 to 5</head>
        <description>
            By the use of points Alias 1 to 5 the template can be added
            up to five aliases which will be added as soon as the template
            is used to create a new site based on it.
            Because it is usefull to add at least a "postmaster" and
            "webmaster" for every site, the process can be automized
            in a immense way.
            The B&amp;F options is for applying the "Bounce and Forward"
            feature to the aliases. For more details see help file of
            Alias Management.
        </description>
    </section>
</help>